https://www.kwiktickets.net/privacy_policy.html

Shopping Cart 0WelcomeGuest CustomerMy Account Home
Products Auction Bidder Cards, Auction FormsAuction Bid Card With or Without Stub No NumbersAuction Bid Card With Stub
1Giant Auction Number Cards With StubAuction Bid Card With Stub
2Auction Number CardsStock Auction Bid Form 2 PartStock Auction Bid Form 3 PartBudget Black and White Raffle TicketsBest SellersBudget Raffle 2 XQuick TicketJumbo Ticket LandscapeJumbo Cash Bash/Gun Bash TicketShort Raffle Stapled in Books TicketAdmit One TicketBudget RaffleCalendar TicketsHalf TicketShort Jumbo Ticket2 Number Jumbo Ticket5 number Lottery TicketsBig TicketShort Half Ticket12x18 Calendar Poster25 number Lottery Tickets10 Number Jumbo TicketSports BoardsCovid 19 Single Use MenusNEWSingle Use Menus 8.5"x14"Black & White CopiesBusiness CardsStandard Business CardsChinese Auction TicketsChinese Auction Tickets B&WChinese Auction Full ColorStrip 10 with Stub ColorStrip 5 Stub-3Strip 10 HorizontalStrip 10 with StubStrip 5 StubStrip 16 with StubSTRIP 5 STUB COLORCoat and Claim Check Tickets2 Part Coat and Claim Check3 Part Coat and Claim Check4 Part Coat and Claim CheckStock 2 Part Coat ChecksStrip And Sheet TicketsStrip 10 with Stub ColorStrip 5 Stub-35 number Lottery TicketsStrip 10 HorizontalStrip 10 with StubStrip 5 Stub25 number Lottery TicketsStrip 16 with StubSTRIP 5 STUB COLORDoor Hangers/ Door Hanger BlanksLaser and Ink Jet Compatible-Blank Die Cut Door Hangers - 2 Up - No Cutting RequiredLaser and Ink Jet Compatible-Blank Die Cut Door Hangers - 3 Up - NO Cutting RequiredLaser and Ink Jet Compatible-Blank Die Cut Door Hangers - 2 Up - Cutting RequiredFREE SHIPPINGLaser and Ink Jet Compatible-Blank Die Cut Door Hangers - 3 Up - Cutting RequiredDoor Hangers 4" x 7"Die Cut FundraisersDie Cut Badge / Shield 3.5"x 6"Die Cut Butter Fly 5"x5"Die Cut Circle 5"x5"Die Cut Oval 4.5"x3.5"Die Cut Oval 8"x5"Marketing MaterialsPosters2 Part NCR Forms 5.5"x8.5"2 Part NCR Forms 8.5x11Standard Business CardsDoor Hangers 8.5 x 3.5 inFlyers One Side ColorPostcardsSports BoardsFull Color TicketsRST80Full Color Quick Ticket - 2.125x5.5RST90RST110Multi Stub Tickets5 number Lottery TicketsBudget Raffle ColorFull Color Event Ticket - 2.625" x 6.75"12x18 Calendar Poster25 number Lottery TicketsSTRIP 5 STUB COLORZombiemHunting PermitValet and Parking TicketsStock Parking TicketVP5 3 Part Valet TicketsVisitor Parking TicketVP64 Part Valet Tickets VP4Numbered 3 Part Valet Parking PermitVP7 4 Part Valet Parking Permit5 Part Valet Tickets VP5Hanging 4 Part Valet Tickets/ Double Sided VP4DieCutHanging Numbered 3 Part Valet PermitVP 15 Oversized 4 Part Valet TicketsVP 2 Hanging Numbered Parking PermitTemporary Parking TicketHandicapped Parking TicketPrintable Raffle Ticket BlanksBlank 8 Up Pre Numbered Perforated Raffle Ticket SheetsLaser and Ink Jet Compatible-Blank Die Cut Door Hangers - 2 Up - No Cutting RequiredLaser and Ink Jet Compatible-Blank Die Cut Door Hangers - 3 Up - NO Cutting RequiredLaser and Ink Jet Compatible-Blank Die Cut Door Hangers - 2 Up - Cutting RequiredFREE SHIPPINGLaser and Ink Jet Compatible-Blank Die Cut Door Hangers - 3 Up - Cutting Required3 Up Jumbo Blank Tear Apart Raffle Ticket SheetzNotepadsNote PadsNotepads - 4.25x5.5Party Reservation FormPrescription FormsCMS Prescription Laser Sheets1 Part CMS Prescription Pads Size 4 ¼” x 5 ½”2 Part CMS Prescription Pads Size 4 ¼” x 5 ½”1 Part CMS Prescription Pads Large - Size 5 ½” x 8 ½”2 Part CMS Prescription Pads Large - Size 5 ½” x 8 ½”NCR Sales SlipsNEW Product2 Part NCR Forms 5.5"x8.5"2 Part NCR Forms 8.5x11Reserve Seating & Concert TicketsRST80RST90RST110Multi Stub TicketsFull Color Event Ticket - 2.625" x 6.75"CDC COVID-19 POSTERSNEW Face Mask poster 12"x15"No Visitors Poster 15"x12"Please-Read.pdf poster 12"x15"Stop the spread of germs poster 12"x15"What you need to know poster 12"x15"What you need to know poster 12"x15"How to Protect Yourself and Others poster 12"x15"Line Starts Here Poster 15"x12"red-arrow-sign 15"x12"Stay Healthy Wash Your Hands Poster 12"x15"What to do if you are sick poster 12"x15"30 Days to Slow the Spread Poster 15"x12"Symptoms of Coronavirus Disease 2019 poster 12"x15.25"Wash Your Hands Poster 11"x17"View All
About Us
Contact Us
Login / Register
* Email ID * Password LoginForgot password?New User ?Register Request a Quote 0Privacy PolicyHomePrivacy PolicyEffective January 1st, 2018
kwiktickets.com inc values its customers and respects their privacy. We collect customer information in an effort to improve your shopping experience and to communicate with you about our products, services, contests, and promotions. kwiktickets.com inc recognizes that it must maintain and use customer information responsibly. We do not sell or rent the information you provide to us online to third parties. However, we do share your information with third parties under certain circumstances as detailed below.
This policy describes the personal information we collect about you, why we collect it, how we use it and when we share it with third parties. Our policy also describes the choices you can make about how we collect and use your information. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, click here to contact kwiktickets.com inc.com customer service via email or write us at:
Attn: Customer Service 109 S Mt. Vernon Ave, Uniontown,  PA 15401
If our information practices change in the future, we will let you know by posting the policy changes on our Web site or by communicating directly with you. We will notify you of any such change before we use your information in a manner not previously disclosed in our privacy policy. You will have the opportunity at that time to opt out of any new use of your information.
WHAT WE COLLECT
We collect information (such as your name, email address, mailing address, phone) that you provide when you place an order, save your information with us or participate in a contest, promotion or survey. We also maintain a record of your product interests and your purchases online.
HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION
When you make an online purchase from kwiktickets.com inc, we use your information to process your order. We will also send you emails to confirm your order, and we may need to contact you via phone, postal mail or email if we have other questions regarding your order. In addition, you will be automatically signed up to receive email updates about our products, services, contests, and promotions.
When you save your information with kwiktickets.com inc, you will also be automatically signed up to receive email updates. If you participate in a contest or promotion (online or over the phone), you may choose to receive email updates about our products, services, contests, and promotions.
If at any time you would like us to remove you from our email or postal mailing lists, feel free to contact kwiktickets.com inc customer service at support@kwiktickets.com inc.com .Please be sure to include full name and any other relevant information. If you have previously asked to be removed from our email list, we will not sign you up for email updates if you place an order over the Internet. Please note that it may take up to 6 weeks to remove your from our list.
From time to time, we may also send you emails to help us learn more about your shopping preferences. In addition, we may use information about your product interests and purchases to help us improve our site design and your shopping experience. If you make a purchase online or over the phone, we may also send you notices about our products, services, contests and promotions through postal mail.
To serve you better, we may combine information you give us online and in our stores as well as information about your product interests and purchases. In addition, we may combine information you provide with demographic information that is publicly available. We use this combined information to enhance and personalize your shopping experience with us, and to communicate with you by email or postal mail about our products, services, contests, and promotions that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information as described above, please contact kwiktickets.com inc service by emailing support@kwiktickets.com inc.com
THIRD PARTY TRANSACTIONSWe do not share any of your information with any third pary.
CHILDREN'S PRIVACY
We at kwiktickets.com inc are concerned about the safety of children when they use the Internet. Consistent with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18 without prior verifiable parental consent.
If we become aware that a subscriber is under the age of 18 and has signed up without prior verifiable parental consent, we will remove his or her personally identifiable information from our files.
COOKIES
A cookie is a small data file that Web sites often store on your computer's hard drive when you visit their sites. A cookie may contain information (such as a unique user ID), that is used to track the pages of the sites you've visited. We use cookies but do not store personally identifiable information in your cookie.
We use cookies in order to improve your shopping experience. When you visit kwiktickets.com inc, your cookie helps us keep track of your order as you shop at our site. If you have saved your information with us, your cookie allows us to recognize you when you return to our site and provides you with access to your account information. If you saved your information with or order from us, we also use cookies to monitor and maintain information about your use of our site. If you have not saved your information with or ordered from us, we may monitor and maintain information about your use of our Web site in a manner that does not identify you. In either case, this information helps us serve you better by improving our site design, as well as our products, services, contests, and promotions.
We also use cookies to track and maintain the identity of the Web site you visited immediately prior to ours to further improve our site design and to fulfill contracts with our business partners. We do not otherwise track any information about your use of other Web sites.
You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you turn off cookies, though, we will not be able to track your order or enable you to make a purchase from our site. Nor will we be able to recognize you as a signed up user to allow you access to your account information.Sign up for emails and get 5% off your first order!SubscribeProduct CategoryProduct CategoryAuction Bidder Cards, Auction FormsBudget Black and White Raffle TicketsBest SellersCovid 19 Single Use MenusNEWBusiness CardsChinese Auction TicketsCoat and Claim Check TicketsStrip And Sheet TicketsDoor Hangers/ Door Hanger BlanksDie Cut FundraisersMarketing MaterialsFull Color TicketsValet and Parking TicketsPrintable Raffle Ticket BlanksNotepadsPrescription FormsNCR Sales SlipsNEW ProductReserve Seating & Concert TicketsCDC COVID-19 POSTERSNEW Quick Links Privacy & Security Policy
Request a Quote
Terms & Conditions Contact UsKwiktickets
109 S Mt. Vernon Ave
Uniontown, PA 15401 1-877-515-5219Fax: 724-438-6050orders@kwiktickets.com
